<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ops on the Pirate Baby</title>
    <link>http://0.0.0.0:1313/tags/ops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ops on the Pirate Baby</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://0.0.0.0:1313/tags/ops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The one where a picture of your dog broke your CD pipeline</title>
      <link>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/the_one_where_a_picture_of_your_dog_broke_the_cd_pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/the_one_where_a_picture_of_your_dog_broke_the_cd_pipeline/</guid>
      <description>It starts out innocent enough, on a frozen New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve afternoon. You are doing some final documentation cleanup - because it is New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve and not the best time for the team to be rolling out fresh feature code, and because updating the repo docs is usually a worthwhile endeavor in moments like this as part of good code hygiene. Being the clever and hilarious documentation author that you are, you hyperlink a picture of your dog Bash to a bash code block (pure pun magnificence, I might add).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Complete Containerized CD Pipeline With AWS and Cloudflare for 2024</title>
      <link>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/complete_cd_with_aws_codepipeline_ecs_and_cloudflare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/complete_cd_with_aws_codepipeline_ecs_and_cloudflare/</guid>
      <description>Recently I went about standing up a fresh Continuous Delivery pipeline for a new project. The project is a relatively standard containerized stack with nothing exceptional to speak of, and as our exploratory work was already in AWS I decided to launch this CD in AWS CodePipeline. Furthermore, we wanted to dogfood our long-term infra management (this project is infra abstraction/automation software) and so opted not to use TerraForm or CloudFormation templates - that way we could have a fully &amp;ldquo;Clickops&amp;rsquo;d&amp;rdquo; infrastructure for our tools to reclaim and manage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Nomenclature</title>
      <link>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/why_data_scientists_are_so_bad_at_naming_things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/why_data_scientists_are_so_bad_at_naming_things/</guid>
      <description>I have a working theory that most of the Data Scientists working today developed their naming conventions by watching Star Trek: The Next Generation in the 90s.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
