<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ml on the Pirate Baby</title>
    <link>http://0.0.0.0:1313/tags/ml/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ml on the Pirate Baby</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://0.0.0.0:1313/tags/ml/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>50 First Dates With MemGPT</title>
      <link>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/50_first_dates_with_memgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/50_first_dates_with_memgpt/</guid>
      <description>preamble The drive home from the movie theater was not going well. My then-girlfriend sat arms crossed in the passenger seat, the red glow from the traffic light matching her mood. &amp;ldquo;You can&amp;rsquo;t just let it be romantic. Why do you have to ruin everything!?!&amp;rdquo; We had just seen 50 First Dates, a classic Sandler/Barrymore romance about a woman who&amp;rsquo;s brain injury prevents her from forming long-term memories. In the movie, Lucy (Barrymore) constructs her own &amp;ldquo;external memory&amp;rdquo; via her diary; a clever plot device, but one that required suspension of disbelief that I just could not abide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Indian Summer for Old Programmers</title>
      <link>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/an_indian_summer_for_old_programmers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/an_indian_summer_for_old_programmers/</guid>
      <description>History The most money I have ever made was my years spent selling motorcycles. Software Engineering is by all means a lucrative profession, and I&amp;rsquo;ve never been the starving artist developer who prizes a compelling mission over a compelling paycheck. But the years I sold motorcycles - between 2003 and 2008 - coincided with a wave of temporary insanity in the US real estate market. Heretofore normal people became mad with the sudden access to &amp;ldquo;wealth,&amp;rdquo; in the form of massive home equity reserves they could spend as easily as cash via HELOC checkbooks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The one where a picture of your dog broke your CD pipeline</title>
      <link>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/the_one_where_a_picture_of_your_dog_broke_the_cd_pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/the_one_where_a_picture_of_your_dog_broke_the_cd_pipeline/</guid>
      <description>It starts out innocent enough, on a frozen New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve afternoon. You are doing some final documentation cleanup - because it is New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve and not the best time for the team to be rolling out fresh feature code, and because updating the repo docs is usually a worthwhile endeavor in moments like this as part of good code hygiene. Being the clever and hilarious documentation author that you are, you hyperlink a picture of your dog Bash to a bash code block (pure pun magnificence, I might add).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Nomenclature</title>
      <link>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/why_data_scientists_are_so_bad_at_naming_things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/why_data_scientists_are_so_bad_at_naming_things/</guid>
      <description>I have a working theory that most of the Data Scientists working today developed their naming conventions by watching Star Trek: The Next Generation in the 90s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Engineering</title>
      <link>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/prompt_engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://0.0.0.0:1313/posts/prompt_engineering/</guid>
      <description>The world never ceases to be filled with new things, and that is exciting. New things are great, but as they come with a learning curve - not the least of which is the language surrounding them. Like when the first coffee shop opened in the little town where I went to college in the late 90s, and we learned to order “express-o” (which was named that, logically, because it was like coffee but faster).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
